[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You need a Swiss ball to build a stronger chest and shoulders.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As a cheaper substitute for which of these precious stones is the synthetic cubic zirconia used?", "correct_answer": "Diamond", "incorrect_answers": ["Peridot", "Goshenite", "Opal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the beginning of the 1973 film The Exorcist an archaeological dig was taking place in what country?", "correct_answer": "Iraq", "incorrect_answers": ["Iran", "South Africa", "Egypt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "William Friedkin vehemently opposed the casting of Gene Hackman in The French Connection. Which of these actors were NOT considered to play Popeye Doyle?", "correct_answer": "Lee Marvin", "incorrect_answers": ["Jackie Gleason", "Steve McQueen", "Paul Newman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1996 movie Independence Day starred Will Smith, Jeff Goldblum and Bill Paxton.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What prolific 19th century novelist wrote The Leatherstocking Tales, a series of novels featuring frontiersman Natty Bumppo?", "correct_answer": "James Fenimore Cooper", "incorrect_answers": ["James Flint", "James Clavell", "James Ellroy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lions are inactive about 20 hours per day.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which are the endocrine systems so-called instant messengers used to affect distant cells within specific organs?", "correct_answer": "Hormones", "incorrect_answers": ["Nephrons", "Neurons", "Acids"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1980 comedy movie starred Chevy Chase and Bill Murray, and contained the funny line Hey, everybody! Were all gonna get laid!?", "correct_answer": "Caddyshack", "incorrect_answers": ["Victor Victoria", "The Jerk", "Nine to Five"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The following quote is from which hit movie?  \nYou can be too old for a lot of things, but youre never too old to be afraid.", "correct_answer": "Home Alone", "incorrect_answers": ["Fat Albert", "The Little Rascals", "Memento"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What objects do we call translucent?", "correct_answer": "Objects that transmit light and scatter it", "incorrect_answers": ["Objects that reflect all light specularly (i.e. in the manner of a mirror)", "Objects that absorb all wavelengths", "Objects that transmit light but do not scatter it"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The great medieval artist, Albrect Durer wrote a textbook in this subject.", "correct_answer": "Geometry", "incorrect_answers": ["Architecture", "Civil Engineering", "Cooking"]}]